Zak Schenck

Professional Summary

I am a proficient Web Developer from Hingham, Massachusetts. I am always striving to learn about the field's newest and cutting edge technologies and frameworks. I have knowledge of server side development, but have always specialized in the Frontend.

Accomplishments

Some of my work:

- E-commerce Page https://zakschenck.github.io/interactive-product-page/
- React.js countries API application

https://splendid-concha-079f80.netlify.app/

- Pokedex API application https://zakschenck.github.io/pokedex-app/
- Tic Tac Toe Application https://zakschenck.github.io/tic-tac-toe/
- Password Generator

https://zakschenck.github.io/password-generator/

Work History

Bay State Community Services - Office Data Entry Clerk

Quincy, MA

08/2021 - Current

- Completed data entry tasks with accuracy and efficiency.
- Scanned documents and saved in database to keep records of essential organizational information.
- Compiled data and reviewed information for accuracy prior to input.

Stop & Shop - Grocery Clerk

Hingham, MA

03/2019 - 03/2020

- Assisted customers by finding items quickly to boost store satisfaction rates.
- Pleasantly greeted customers and provided prompt and courteous service.

■ zackschenck@gmail.com

(781) 635-6303

Hingham, MA 02043

Website, Portfolio, Profiles

- Personal Website: https://zakschenck.github.io/portfoliowebsite/
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/zak-schenck-104792222/
- https://github.com/ZakSchenck

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- React
- Git/NPM

Education

Career Foundry

Certificate: Intro To Frontend Web Developer

06/2017

Quincy College

Quincy, MA

GED

• Used pallet jacks to move merchandise to sales floor for stocking. **Bay State Community Services - Computer Assistant Intern** Quincy, MA 01/2017 - 02/2017 • Updated company computer applications across multiple job sites.